<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My Favourite Things on Home</title>
    <link>https://greengypsy.github.io/my-favourite-things/</link>
    <description>Recent content in My Favourite Things on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://greengypsy.github.io/my-favourite-things/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Becoming a technical writer</title>
      <link>https://greengypsy.github.io/my-favourite-things/posts/post-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://greengypsy.github.io/my-favourite-things/posts/post-2/</guid>
      <description>What is technical writing? Technical writing is the art of translating complex topics in simple terms, usually in a written format. Technical writers create all sorts of material such as:
User manuals Quick start guides Reports Presentations Papers Technical writers work in many different sectors from mining and manufacturing, to IT and the public sector.
What sparked my interest in technical writing Even in my uni days, I was always interested in explaining technology and technical concepts at a high level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building my first website</title>
      <link>https://greengypsy.github.io/my-favourite-things/posts/post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 15:04:59 +1030</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://greengypsy.github.io/my-favourite-things/posts/post-1/</guid>
      <description>Wanting to create a website Have you ever wanted to create your own website?
Don&amp;rsquo;t want to rely on Wordpress and Squarespace but don&amp;rsquo;t want to completely build it from scratch?
Me too! So, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to create a website using Hugo.
Why I&amp;rsquo;m using Hugo What is Hugo? According to Hugo&amp;rsquo;s own website, Hugo is a &amp;ldquo;static site generator&amp;rdquo;.
In other words, Hugo is a software application that lets you generate a HTML website from a set of template files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://greengypsy.github.io/my-favourite-things/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://greengypsy.github.io/my-favourite-things/about-me/</guid>
      <description>I am a technical writer from Adelaide with a combined interest of writing and technology.
Here is a list of projects I have worked on as a technical writer:
Restructuring the Maptek Evolution documentation. Creating a Quick Start Guide for Maptek DomainMCF. Profile writing for the Australian Public Service Commission (not yet published). Contributing to the successful 2022 Google Season of Docs OpenMS project. If you have any questions, get in touch today</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://greengypsy.github.io/my-favourite-things/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://greengypsy.github.io/my-favourite-things/contact/</guid>
      <description>If you have any questions, feel free to reach out to me using the form below.
I will try to get back to you as soon as possible.
Your Name Email Address An email address is required. Message </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Posts</title>
      <link>https://greengypsy.github.io/my-favourite-things/posts-by-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://greengypsy.github.io/my-favourite-things/posts-by-date/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
